Guide to the KUHT Records 1997-006
University of Houston Libraries Special Collections
- Photographs and Slides
  - Galveston Film Project (Box 446, Folder 38)
  - Gift of Learning (Box 446, Folder 39)
  - Heartbreak Turtle Publicity (Box 446, Folder 40)
  - ID Slides Raw Material (Box 446, Folder 41)
  - Is Teenager a Disease or What Girls? (Box 446, Folder 42)
  - Jacob's Well (Box 446, Folder 43)
  - JD's Journal - John Davenport (Box 446, Folder 44)
  - JD's Journal - Fortune Cookies (Box 446, Folder 45)
  - Joske's P.I. Display (Box 446, Folder 46)
  - Ken Brantley Productions (Box 446, Folder 47)
  - KUHT - B&W Show Masks (Box 446, Folder 48)
  - KUHT - Remote Truck (Box 446, Folder 49)
  - KUHT TV U of H (Box 446, Folder 50)
  - KUHT Stock Photos - A Matter of Time (Box 446, Folder 51)
  - KUHT Stock Photos - Brazilian Express (Box 446, Folder 52)
  - KUHT Stock Photos - Christmas Festival of Harps (Box 446, Folder 53)
  - KUHT Stock Photos - Couple in Car, photo: Dan Richardson, March 14, 1980 (Box 446, Folder 54)
  - KUHT Stock Photos - Friday Local (Box 446, Folder 55)
  - KUHT Stock Photos - The Greenroom (Box 446, Folder 56)
  - KUHT Stock Photos - Miscellaneous (Box 446, Folder 57)
  - KUHT Stock Photos - P.T.V. Potpourri (Box 446, Folder 58)
  - KUHT Stock Photos - San Francisco Mime Troupe (Box 446, Folder 59)
  - KUHT Stock Photos - Sports Unlimited (Box 446, Folder 60)
  - KUHT Studio Lobby (Box 446, Folder 61)
  - La Reina De Selva (Box 446, Folder 62-63)
  - Late Night America (Box 446, Folder 64)
  - League of Women Voters - Debates (Box 446, Folder 65)
  - Legacy of Sound (Box 446, Folder 66)
  - Lorenz (Box 446, Folder 67)
  - Los Pastores, Stills and Proofs (Box 446, Folder 68)
  - March of Dimes (Box 446, Folder 69)
  - McNeil/Lehrer (Box 446, Folder 70)
  - Membership Premiums (Box 446, Folder 71)
  - Miscellaneous Portrait (Box 446, Folder 72)
  - Miscellaneous Enlarged Photos (Box 446, Folder 73)
  - Miscellaneous Photos (Box 446, Folder 74-80)
  - Miscellaneous Photos, Docs (Box 446, Folder 81-82)
  - New Visions, photo: D. Dale (Box 446, Folder 83)
  - Old Folks (Box 446, Folder 84)
  - On the Line (Box 446, Folder 85)
  - Pat Paulson - ACT Promo (Box 446, Folder 86)
  - The Persuaders (Box 446, Folder 87)
  - Phoenician Ship (Box 446, Folder 88)
  - Political Show (Box 446, Folder 89)
  - Political Shows (Box 447, Folder 1)
  - #1705 A Portrait of Trinidad and Tobago (Box 447, Folder 2)
  - Production Publicity (Box 447, Folder 3)
  - Project 26 (Box 447, Folder 4)
  - Public Times - Schlitz Ad, photo: D. Dale (Box 447, Folder 5)
  - Psychiatry (Box 447, Folder 6)
  - Public Times - Marcel Marceau (Box 447, Folder 7)
  - Round Top Site Survey - Alan Suhanen (Box 447, Folder 8)
  - Satellite (Box 447, Folder 9)
  - Set Documentation (Box 447, Folder 10)
  - Signing with Cindy - B&W Contact Sheets (Box 447, Folder 11)
  - Silent Challenge (Box 447, Folder 12)
  - Space Watch (Box 447, Folder 13)
  - Spotlight Showcase (Box 447, Folder 14-15)
  - Star Photos - James Stewart, "It's a Wonderful Life," Johnny Carson (Box 447, Folder 16)
  - Star Photos - Miscellaneous including John Wayne, Hitler, Charles Lindbergh (Box 447, Folder 17)
  - Star Photos - Musicians/Singers including Glenn Miller, Yanni (Box 447, Folder 18)
  - Star Photos - "Stand and Deliver," Lou Diamond Philips (Box 447, Folder 19)
  - Star Photos - "The Wealthy Barber" with David Chilton (Box 447, Folder 20)
  - Station and Station Personnel (Box 447, Folder 21)
  - Stock Photos - Empty Buildings (Box 447, Folder 22)
  - Talk Point - Hackerman (Box 447, Folder 23)
  - Tattoo - Bayou City (Box 447, Folder 24)
  - Tennis Classic (Box 447, Folder 25)
  - Texas Raider (Box 447, Folder 26)
  - This Is My Home - It's Not For Sale (Box 447, Folder 27)
  - Together with the People (Box 447, Folder 28)
  - TV Radio Format (Box 447, Folder 29)
  - TV Worth Watching (Box 447, Folder 30)
  - United Way Telethon Set Photos (Box 447, Folder 31)
  - Viewpoint SE Asia, originally Vietnam Pacific (Box 447, Folder 32)
  - Wall Street Week (Box 447, Folder 33)
  - Act for 8 (Box 448, Folder 1)
  - Aerials Houston (Box 448, Folder 2)
  - Anniversary Logo (Box 448, Folder 3)
  - Auction Slides - San Leon Marina, 18K Gold Watch, KTRH News Radio, Opera, 1989 (Box 448, Folder 4)
  - Auction Slides - Cypress Lake, #9126, 1988 (Box 448, Folder 5)
  - Auction Slides - Point Aquarius Lot (Box 448, Folder 6)
  - Auction Slides - Rayburn Country (Box 448, Folder 7)
  - Auction Slides - South Shore Harbor, April 25, 1988 (Box 448, Folder 8)
  - Auction Slides - Answ. Amer. / Able-1, #9190, 1989 (Box 448, Folder 9)
  - Auction Slides - Pemberton Security, #9092, 1989 (Box 448, Folder 10)
  - Auction Slides - National Guardian Alarm, April 25, 1988 (Box 448, Folder 11)
  - Auction Slides - Kensington Executive Suites, April 18, 1988 (Box 448, Folder 12)
  - Auction Slides - Jim's Carpet, April 29, 1989 (Box 448, Folder 13)
  - Auction Slides - The Clean Air and Water Store, April 28, 1989 (Box 448, Folder 14)
  - Auction Slides - Gulf Coast Lawn Sprinkler, May 1, 1989 (Box 448, Folder 15)
  - Auction Slides - Cooper Alarm, 1988 (Box 448, Folder 16)
  - Auction Slides - Norman Furniture, April 14, 1988 (Box 448, Folder 17)
  - Auction Slides - Viletta China, April 1988 (Box 448, Folder 18)
  - Auction Slides - Stages (Box 448, Folder 19)
  - Auction Slides - Schlitzberger's Monuments, 1987-1988 (Box 448, Folder 20)
  - Auction Slides - Grace Memorial, Forest Lawn (Box 448, Folder 21)
  - Auction Slides - Eternity Park (Box 448, Folder 22)
  - Auction Slides - Sheldon Pollack Corporation (Box 448, Folder 23)
  - Auction Slides - Waddell's Fine Furniture, Hallmark-Carrier Air Conditioner, April 27, 1987 (Box 448, Folder 24)
  - Auction Slides - Montesano's Italian Restaurant, Am Pet Services, April 30, 1987 (Box 448, Folder 25)
  - Auction Slides - Kidder Peabody & Co. Granite Monument (Box 448, Folder 26)
  - Auction Slides - Sage Plaza 1 yr. Office Lease, Houston Tracker Satellite (Box 448, Folder 27)
  - Auction Slides - Jewish Community Center (Box 448, Folder 28)
  - Auction Slides - Electronic Technicians, The Women's Hospital (Box 448, Folder 29)
  - Auction Slides - Family Birthing Center, Alpha Omega Arabians (Box 448, Folder 30)
  - Auction Slides - River Oaks Plant House Unicorn Topiary, Elite Services (Box 448, Folder 31)
  - Auction Slides - Tony Lyons Corp., Tabriz Kahn Bus (Box 448, Folder 32)
  - Auction Slides - Bayou City - Georgia's, Royal Gaelord Restaurant (Box 448, Folder 33)
  - Auction Slides - Allegro Travel Services, Capt. Dean's Charter (Box 448, Folder 34)
  - Auction Slides - Premier Co., Houston Home and Garden (Box 448, Folder 35)
  - Auction Slides - Logo (Box 448, Folder 36)
  - Auction Slides - Miscellaneous (Box 448, Folder 37)
  - Boats (Box 448, Folder 38)
  - Boxing (Box 448, Folder 39)
  - Circus (Box 448, Folder 40)
  - Construction (Box 448, Folder 41)
  - Construction of "Tall Tower" (Box 448, Folder 42)
  - Education Co-op (Box 448, Folder 43)
  - GRETA (Box 448, Folder 44)
  - Hall of Fame (Box 448, Folder 45)
  - Hot Air Balloons (Box 448, Folder 46)
  - KUHF (Box 448, Folder 47)
  - Logos I (Box 448, Folder 48)
  - Logos II (Box 448, Folder 49)
  - Logos III (Box 448, Folder 50)
  - Logos IV (Box 448, Folder 51)
  - Membership Drive (Box 448, Folder 52)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 448, Folder 53)
  - Outside Shots of KUHT Building (Box 448, Folder 54)
  - Printmaking Pilot (Box 448, Folder 55)
  - Schools (Box 448, Folder 56)
  - TSU (Box 448, Folder 57)
  - Enlarged portrait of man in striped tie, working in an office (Ovs box 449a)
  - Whiteboard: Zero to Sixty, script and numbers (Ovs box 449a)
  - Enlarged photo of KUHT studio, seen from control room [5th Floor Master Control] - extensive cracks in photo surface, [1953] (Ovs box 449a)
  - NAM Thanks KUHT, April 20, 1955 (Ovs box 449a)
  - 25th Anniversary Auction photo by Dan Richardson (Ovs box 449a)
  - Two women and one man on couch reading a magazine in front of cameras, picture labeled Bernard H. Goodmand (Ovs box 449a)
    On beige poster board, in large folder with historic photos of KUHT first opening
  - Two photographs mounted on board captioned "Purposes of KUHT are Three-fold," Dr. John Meaney, film director, instructs a student on the use of film; and "Operation of a Boom Mike," Assistant director, Pat Welch, gives the student some pointers (Ovs box 449a)
  - Disbound scrapbook page captioned "Superintendent of Public Schools, Dr. W. E. Moreland..." (Ovs box 449a)
  - Disbound scrapbook page captioned "The first equipment arrives..." and "Construction is underway..." (Ovs box 449a)
  - Disbound scrapbook page captioned "On the air..." and "Cartoons to music..." (Ovs box 449a)
  - Disbound scrapbook page captioned "These students..." and "Graduate student..." (Ovs box 449a)
  - Disbound scrapbook page captioned "Art students..." and "Lighting is elaborate..." (Ovs box 449a)
  - Disbound scrapbook page captioned "Control room work..." (Ovs box 449a)
  - Disbound scrapbook page captioned "Scripts and rehearsals..." and "Students..." (Ovs box 449a)
  - Disbound scrapbook page captioned "Rehearsals begin..." and "Long hours of practice..." (Ovs box 449a)
  - Proclamation of Educational Television Week by Mayor Louie Welch, August 29, 1966 (Ovs box 449a)
  - Richard Uray, director, behind KUHT newsstand (Ovs box 449a)
  - Dr. Kemmerer, Miss Hennock, and H.R. Cullen get together at the dedication (Ovs box 449a)
    In large folder with historic photos of KUHT first opening
  - Two photographs mounted on board captioned "Planning of a Dream" Dr. W.W. Kemmerer, President of the University of Houston, and H.R. Cullen, Chairman of the Board of Regents, talking; and "First Steps" Dr. Kemmerer and Max Jacobs, President of KNUZ-TV, looking at drawings for a Texas TV Center (Ovs box 449a)
  - Disbound scrapbook page captioned "One of the first (and worst) ID Slides...", 1953 (Ovs box 449b)
  - Disbound scrapbook page: Vic Damone and Jo Ann Breneks stand at KUHF-FM microphone, [1950s] (Ovs box 449b)
  - Disbound scrapbook page: Dr. Rogers's mathematics telecourse, 1958-1965 (Ovs box 449b)
  - Disbound scrapbook page: KUHT control room [man in Channel 8 jumpsuit] (Ovs box 449b)
  - Disbound scrapbook page: KUHF host sings into microphone while accompanied by the piano (Ovs box 449b)
  - Disbound scrapbook page: KUHF-FM host is shown a boat's control panel (Ovs box 449b)
  - Disbound scrapbook page: Speech Therapy telecourse (Woman on set with three cameramen) (Ovs box 449b)
  - Disbound scrapbook page: Portrait of Kathy Landers on set (Ovs box 449b)
    On gray poster board
  - Disbound scrapbook page: Bernie Burrus, Martha Cayson, and Joan Ryba on KUHT show set, 1953 (Ovs box 449b)
  - Disbound scrapbook page: Channel eight staff photo with subjects identified, 1956 (Ovs box 449b)
  - Disbound scrapbook page: Aerial view of the Texas A&M campus (Ovs box 449b)
  - Disbound scrapbook page: KUHT studio, seen from control room [5th Floor Master Control] (Ovs box 449b)
  - Disbound scrapbook page: Portrait of KUHT microphone boom operator (Ovs box 449b)
  - Disbound scrapbook page: Ernest Brock and Jim Bauer on location at the Dallas ISD Administration Building (Ovs box 449b)
  - Disbound scrapbook page: KUHT camera operator with child behind the camera (Ovs box 449b)
  - Disbound scrapbook page: View of KUHT tower (Ovs box 449b)
  - TSU dancers perform on "People are Taught to be Different" (Ovs box 449b)
  - Man hosts "Western World Literature" (Ovs box 449b)
  - Man teaches telecourse, "Reading for Writing and Research" (Ovs box 449b)
  - Man demonstrates audio equipment on screen (Ovs box 449b)
  - Dr. John Rider and Dr. Hubertus Srughold holding model spacecraft on ser of "Doctors in Space" (Ovs box 449b)
  - Woman reads on set of children's show (Ovs box 449b)
  - Aerial view of the University of Houston campus, approximately 1950s (Ovs box 449b)
  - Woman whispering to a man behind camera on set, November 3, 1953 (Ovs box 449b)
  - Cameramen film two boys playing checkers (Ovs box 449b)
  - Newspaper collage, 1950 (Ovs box 449b)
  - Newspaper collage, 1953 (Ovs box 449b)
  - Enlarged photograph of the first remote van at KUHT, 1953 (Ovs box 449b)
  - The first remote van at KUHT, Inscription: KUHT remote truck was donated to the station by the AFL-CIO Education Committee. Parked next to the city school office where Board of Education meetings are telecast regularly., 1953 (Ovs box 449b)
  - 1983 Maggie Awards - honorable mention, presented to KUHT_TV for "A Baby Maybe: to be or not to be a parent" (Ovs box 449c)
  - KUHT - A World Transformed VHS cover (Ovs box 449c)
    On black matte board
  - KUHT - A World Transformed - the cold war is over (Ovs box 449c)
  - TV/Radio Tower, different angle, photo: D. Dale (Ovs box 449c)
  - On the set of a talk show - two men and one woman on couches (Ovs box 449c)
    On matte board
  - Two photographs mounted on board: KUHT 8 promotional items; man in front of cameras (Ovs box 449c)
  - Festival '78 - Fundraising sign and Set, 1978 (Ovs box 449c)
    Two photos on matte board
  - Festival '78 - Set and Switchboard, 1978 (Ovs box 449c)
  - KUHT-TV's first tele-auction with Paul Boesch, May 4, 1971 (Ovs box 449c)
  - Panel discusses the 1973 city council election on set at KUHT [2 copies] (Ovs box 449c)
  - Overhead view of panel discussing the 1973 city council election on set at KUHT [2 copies] (Ovs box 449c)
  - "Once Upon a Printing Press" filming in KUHT studio: Audrey Wrye on set with two puppets. (Ovs box 449c)
  - Portrait of a man (Ovs box 449c)
  - Entrance to KUHT studios at night (Ovs box 449c)
  - Communication Arts Career Day Slides, 1962 (Ovs box 449d)
  - KUHT Transition from local to regional coverage graphic (Ovs box 449d)
  - Dr. Kemmerer, FCC commissioner Frieda Hennock and H. R. Cullen at the dedication of the first educational television station, june 8, 1953 (Ovs box 449d)
  - George Collins fixing light (Ovs box 449d)
  - Henry Du Pris interviewing two guests on KUHT Open House (Ovs box 449d)
  - Four women and one man viewing first telecast (Ovs box 449d)
    Copy of picture in large folder
  - Man with clapperboard on set of "Doctors in Space" with Dr. John Rider and Dr. Hubertus Strughold [2 copies], 1953 (Ovs box 449d)
  - KUHT News filming, 1953 (Ovs box 449d)
  - KUHT - Control Room, front of Bill Hawes book (Ovs box 449d)
  - P.J. Nicholson accepts the KUHT remote truck from Frank Wozencraft and Marty Levine, 1972 (Ovs box 449d)
  - Portrait of Dorothy Sinclair, head of KUHT's GRETA program (Ovs box 449d)
  - Marilyn VanDerbur at a podium (Harry Byrd Kline Celebrity Service) (Ovs box 449d)
  - Full-length view of the KUHT transmitting tower, 4513 Cullen Blvd., 1964 (Ovs box 449d)
  - Dick Cavett publicity headshot, 1977 (Ovs box 449d)
  - Dick Cavett candid publicity headshot and negative, 1978 (Ovs box 449d)
  - Mister Rogers Neighborhood publicity photo (Ovs box 449d)
  - The Metropolitan Opera Presents Il Trovatore publicity photo (Ovs box 449d)
  - Ella Fitzgerald candid publicity headshot and negative, 1978 (Ovs box 449d)
  - Woman with ERA button speaking at podium, 1977 (Ovs box 449d)
  - Man in suit, "Richards" handwritten in corner (Ovs box 449d)
  - Unidentified man in suit (Ovs box 449d)
  - For Children, Saul Steinberg. Institute for the Arts, Rice University, 1971 (Ovs box 449d)
  - Three young women in the foreground and a young man seated on a wall in the background (Ovs box 449d)
  - Young woman and man sitting on couch (Ovs box 449d)
  - Smiling young woman and young man eating lunch (Ovs box 449d)
  - "The Theatre Men" Eight men in tuxedos with woman in formal gown (Ovs box 449d)
    General
    Stamp on back reads, "Please return to Houston Baptist College"
  - Sharon Blair and George Arms at KUHT's 25th Anniversary, 1978 (Ovs box 449d)
  - Party on KUHT set (Ovs box 449d)
  - Keith Smith, camera operator for TeleAuction 1975 (Ovs box 449d)
  - Embryo, caption on verso: "NOVA, Great moments from Nova, Photo Credit: Lennart, Nilsson, Sveriges Tele." (Ovs box 449d)
  - Seal of the University of Houston (Ovs box 449d)
  - Jones Hall by Bob Hague (News on Campus), 1960s (Ovs box 449d)
  - Jones Hall sign by Bob Hague (News on Campus), 1960s (Ovs box 449d)
  - Moody Towers construction (News on Campus), 1960s (Ovs box 449d)
  - Hoffman Hall under construction (News on Campus), 1960s (Ovs box 449d)
  - Underground Satellite construction (News on Campus), 1960s (Ovs box 449d)
  - Law School construction (News on Campus), 1960s (Ovs box 449d)
  - Model, College of Education (News on Campus), 1960s (Ovs box 449d)
  - Model, College of Education, view from above (News on Campus), 1960s (Ovs box 449d)
  - Hilton Hotel and Restaurant College construction (News on Campus), 1960s (Ovs box 449d)
  - Entrance UC Underground 910; air conditioning bldg (News on Campus), 1960s (Ovs box 449d)
  - E. Cullen view to downtown Houston (News on Campus), 1960s (Ovs box 449d)
  - University of St. Thomas sign #1 by Bob Hague (News on Campus) (Ovs box 449d)
  - University of St. Thomas sign #2 by Bob Hague (News on Campus) (Ovs box 449d)
  - University of St. Thomas sign #3 by Bob Hague (News on Campus) (Ovs box 449d)
  - University of St. Thomas sign #4 by Bob Hague (News on Campus) (Ovs box 449d)
  - "You're a Good Man, Charlie Brown" Picture #1, St. Thomas News (Ovs box 449d)
  - "You're a Good Man, Charlie Brown" Picture #2, St. Thomas News (Ovs box 449d)
  - Boom operator (Ovs box 450)
  - Events (Ovs box 450, Folder 1)
  - Art (Ovs box 450, Folder 2)
  - People (Ovs box 450, Folder 3-5)
  - Miscellaneous (Ovs box 450, Folder 6)
  - KUHT Studio (Ovs box 451, Folder 1-2)
  - Productions (Ovs box 451, Folder 3-4)
- Ephemera
  - All Stressed up & Nowhere to Go
    - Brochures and Correspondence (Box 452, Folder 1)
    - All Stressed up & Nowhere to Go!: a guide to dealing with stress and creating a purposeful life, by Bill Crawford, Ph.D. (Box 452)
      Three books
    - Regaining Control: Dealing with Stress vs. Stress Dealing with you movie (Box 452)
    - All Stressed up... XL t-shirt (Box 452)
  - Live at the Woodlands
    - Live at the Woodlands L t-shirts (3) (Box 452)
    - Rough Woodlands Promos, Jeff Clarke 5 spots, betacam tape (Box 452)
  - Quilt Festival 1989
    - 15th Anniversary Logo Bag (Box 452)
    - Quilt Festival disks (2) (Box 452)
    - Quilting International magazines (2) (Box 452)
    - Quilting Festival 1994 Information Packet (Box 452, Folder 2)
- Awards
  - National Association of Educational Broadcasters (NAEB), Certificate of Active Membership, presented to KUHT-TV, 1961 (Box 453)
  - National Educational Television, Award for Excellence in Creative Programming and Community Service, presented to KUHT for "The Wrong End of Main", 1966 (Box 453)
  - International Film & TV Festival of New York, Gold Award, presented to KUHT for "U.S. Chronicle", 1981 (Box 453)
  - Texas Municipal Courts Association, Special Media Award, presented to KUHT-TV, April 24, 1981 (Box 453)
  - International Film & TV Festival of New York, Bronze Award, presented to KUHT-TV for "The Heartbreak Turtle"; Miriam Korshak, Producer-Writer, 1982 (Box 453)
  - Educational Film Library Association, American Film Festival New York City, Honorable Mention, "The Heartbreak Turtle", 1983 (Box 453)
  - Sixth Annual Angel Awards, Award of Merit, Presented to "New Gospel Jubilee", February 17, 1983 (Box 453)
  - The Ohio State University, For Excellence in Educational, Informational, and Public Affairs Broadcasting, The Ohio State Award, Presented to KUHT-TV for "Signing with Cindy", April 27, 1983 (Box 453)
  - The University of Houston, Board of Regents, in recognition and appreciation of its dedication and generous support over a period of thirteen years, presented to KUHT Channel 8, two phots and one letter from William Hawes, June 6, 1983 (Box 453)
  - Corporation for Public Broadcasting, 1984 Public Television Local Program Award for excellence in news, presented to KUHT for "In the Name of God" (Box 453)
  - Educational Film Library Association, Selection for screening at the American Film Festival New York City, presented to "River of Innocence", 1985 (Box 454)
  - 28th Annual International Film and TV Festival of New York, 1985 Gold Medal, presented to KUHT-TV for "Child at Risk"; Miriam Korshak, Executive Producer (Box 454)
    Closed to research for reasons of privacy and confidentiality
  - Houston Police Department, Citation-Public Service Award, presented to KUHT-TV Channel 8, Framed announcemen and Description of Award, August 30, 1985 (Box 454)
  - Houston Police Department, Public Service Award, presented to KUHT-TV Channel 8, August 30, 1985 (Box 454)
  - The National Academy of Television Arts and Sciences, National Finalist for Community Service Award, honors KUHT-TV for "Child at Risk", 1985 (Box 454)
  - The National Academy of Television Arts and Sciences, National Finalist for Community Service Award, honors KUHT-TV for "Child at Risk", 1985 (Box 454)
  - Citizens for Animal Protection, Award of Merit, KUHT-8 for "For Pet's Sake", 1986 (Box 454)
  - H.P.F.F.A. 20th Annual News Awards, Best Documentary - Television, 1st Place, presented to Susan Wright, KUHT TV, 1987 (Box 454)
  - THVN - Houston or Vietnam Public Television, appreciation for airing the Vietnamese New Year Special, presented to KUHT-TV Channel 8, February 17, 1988 (Box 454)
  - Public Telecommunications Institute (NAEB), recognition of sucessful completion of project management of television productions, presented to Miriam Korshak, undated (Box 454)
- Publications
  - Houston Metropolitan, August 1990 (Box 455, Folder 1)
  - Houston Metropolitan, March 1992 (Box 455, Folder 2)
  - Houston Metropolitan, June 1992 (Box 455, Folder 3)
  - Houston Metropolitan, July 1992 (Box 455, Folder 4)
  - Houston Metropolitan, August 1992 (Box 455, Folder 5)
  - Houston Metropolitan, October 1992 (Box 455, Folder 6)
  - Houston Metropolitan, November 1992 (Box 455, Folder 7)
  - Houston Metropolitan, December 1992 (Box 455, Folder 8)
  - Houston Metropolitan, January 1993 (Box 455, Folder 9)
  - Houston Metropolitan, February 1993 (Box 455, Folder 10)
  - Houston Metropolitan, March 1993 (Box 455, Folder 11)
  - Houston Metropolitan, April 1993 (Box 455, Folder 12)
  - Houston Metropolitan, May 1993 (Box 455, Folder 13)
  - Houston Metropolitan, June 1993 (Box 455, Folder 14)
  - Houston Metropolitan, July 1993 (Box 455, Folder 15)
  - Houston Metropolitan, August 1993 (Box 455, Folder 16)
  - Houston Metropolitan, September 1993 (Box 455, Folder 17)
  - Houston Metropolitan, October 1993 (Box 455, Folder 18)
  - Houston Metropolitan, November 1993 (Box 455, Folder 19)
  - Houston Metropolitan, December 1993 (Box 455, Folder 20)
  - Newspaper Clippings - "Acta Diurna", 1971, 1973, 1975, 1976 (Box 455, Folder 21)
  - Newspaper Clippings - KUHF, 1990 (Box 455, Folder 22)
  - Newspaper Clippings - KUHF, 1992 (Box 455, Folder 23)
  - Newspaper Clippings - KUHF, 1993 (Box 455, Folder 24)
  - Newspaper Clippings - KUHF, 1994 (Box 455, Folder 25)
  - Newspaper Clippings - KUHF, 1995 (Box 455, Folder 26)
  - Newspaper Clippings - KUHF, 1997 (Box 455, Folder 27)
  - Newspaper Clippings - KUHF, 1998 (Box 455, Folder 28)
  - Newspaper Clippings - KUHF, 1999 (Box 455, Folder 29)
  - Newspaper Clippings - KUHF, 2000 (Box 455, Folder 30)
  - Newspaper Clippings - KUHF, 2002 (Box 455, Folder 31)
  - Newspaper Clippings - KUHF, 2003 (Box 455, Folder 32)
  - Newspaper Clippings - KUHT, undated (Box 455, Folder 33)
  - Newspaper Clippings - KUHT, 1989 (Box 455, Folder 34)
  - Newspaper Clippings - KUHT, 1991 (Box 455, Folder 35)
  - Newspaper Clippings - KUHT, 1992 (Box 455, Folder 36)
  - Newspaper Clippings - KUHT, 1993 (Box 455, Folder 37)